In a town with no justice, there is only one law... Every man for himself.
Last Man Standing is a crime, action, western film directed by Walter Hill.
John Smith is a mysterious stranger who is drawn into a
vicious war between two Prohibition-era gangs.
In a dangerous game, he switches allegiances from one to
another, offering his services to the highest bidder.
As the death toll mounts, Smith takes the law into his
own hands in a deadly race to stay alive.
John Smith, played by Bruce Willis.
Sheriff Ed Galt, played by Bruce Dern.
Joe Monday, played by William Sanderson.
Hickey, played by Christopher Walken.
Doyle, played by David Patrick Kelly.
Felina, played by Karina Lombard.
Last Man Standing is a 1996 American neo-Western action film
written, produced and directed by Walter Hill.
It stars Bruce Willis, Christopher Walken and Bruce Dern.
The film is a remake of the 1961 Japanese film Yojimbo by Akira
Kurosawa, relocated to the Prohibition-era American South.
In the film, a mysterious gunman (Willis) arrives in a small town ruled by
rivaling gangs, and sets up about playing them against each other.
The film was released by New Line Cinema on September 20, 1996.
It received mixed reviews and was a commercial disappointment.
The film explores themes of prohibition era,
texas, gang war, whiskey, on the run.